learntobeabookkeeper.com 2018-08-18

# Privacy Policy

**Last Revised: March 27, 2017**

Thank you for visiting this web site. Bookkeeper Business Launch, LLC (hereinafter “We”) understand the importance that Internet users place on privacy, and this Privacy Policy describes how we use personal information that is collected at this web site. 

Please read this Privacy Policy before using this web site or submitting any personal information. 

California residents, please also see the “Note To California Residents” section for additional rights that apply to you.

By using this web site, you accept the privacy practices contained in this Privacy Policy. These privacy practices may change from time to time, but any changes will be posted. You are encouraged to review the Privacy Policy whenever you visit the web site to make sure you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

**1.   Information We Collect**

**A. Personally Identifiable Information**

In order to serve our customers, we collect personally identifiable information, like names, addresses, phone numbers, email addresses, and sometimes credit card information when such information is voluntarily submitted by our visitors. We will only use your personal information for the following purposes: (1) to deliver the products and/or services to you that you have requested; (2) to validate your compliance with the terms and conditions; (3) for content improvement and feedback purposes; (4) to reach you, when necessary, regarding your use of the web site or product(s); and (5) for the few situations described below to better serve you.

We will NEVER share your personally identifiable information with third parties unless you have given us explicit permission to do so, such as in order to fulfill a third party offer that you have accepted from us. By permitting us to collect this information, you will be able to receive information on other products and services that may be of interest to you, including related third party offers that we may send to you. You also enable us to personalize your experience with us so that we can provide you with the highest quality of service. 

By submitting your email address on this web site, you agree to receive email from us. You can cancel your participation in any of these email lists at any time by clicking the opt-out link or other unsubscribe option that is included in the respective email. We only send emails to people who have authorized us to contact them, either directly, or through a third party. We do not send unsolicited commercial emails, because we hate spam as much as you do.

By submitting your email address, you also agree to allow us to use your email address for custom audience targeting on sites like Facebook, where we display custom advertising to specific people who have opted-in to receive communications from us. 

In addition, you agree that by submitting your telephone contact information on this web site and/or registering to receive the product and/or service offered herein, such act constitutes a purchase, an inquiry, and/or an application for the purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (ATSR), 16 CFR ‘310 et seq. and any applicable state and local “do not call” regulations. We retain the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the ATSR and the applicable state regulations. 

**B.   Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

We also may collect various types of non-personally identifiable information to help us make your experience more enjoyable, measure site activity to identify future improvements that should be made, and compile aggregate data to help serve site visitors better. 

For example, we may use session and persistent “cookies,” session logs, web beacons, GIF/pixel tags, banner ads, third-party click tracking analytics tools (such as Google Analytics), third party retargeting networks that may display our advertisements to you on other sites that you visit to remind you about us, and third party networks that serve user-requested emails (e.g., for a refer-a-friend email) to collect non-personally identifiable or other aggregated information about site visitors.

Cookies are text files that are used by your computer’s web browser to store your preferences, and enable us to enhance your user experience with our web site. Third party retargeting networks may also use cookies to display our advertisements to you on other sites.  You can learn more about how to opt-out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Emails or newsletters that we send electronically may use techniques such as web beacons or pixel tags to gather email metrics and information to improve the reader’s experience, such as the number of emails that are opened, whether they were forwarded or printed, the type of device from which they were opened, and the location (e.g. city, state, and county) associated with the applicable IP address.

If you visit this web site with an open ID (such as Facebook), you may also be sharing and integrating data with third-party social media sites, and we may track aggregate data about the number of visits to this web site with an open ID, the number of items “liked” on this web site, or items on this web site that you choose to share with a third-party social media site.

Other parties such as advertising partners and analytics companies may also be collecting information about your online activity across various web sites over time. The information collected by those third parties may include identifiers that allow those third parties to tailor the ads that they serve to your computer or other device. 

Because there is not yet a common understanding of how to interpret web browser-based “Do Not Track” signals other than cookies, we do not currently respond to “Do Not Track” signals that are undefined.

Please note that you do have the option to configure most web browsers to NOT accept cookies.  However, be aware that disabling cookies may keep you from having access to some functions or services on our web site or the web-hosted software that runs on our web site.

**2\. Your Access To And Control Over Information**

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do so by contacting us via the email address or phone number provided in the “Contacting Us” section. Please feel free to reach out regarding any of the following information:

  * What data we may have about you, if any;
  * Any changes or corrections you wish to make regarding any of the data you provided;
  * Requesting deletion of any of the data we may have about you; or
  * Express any concerns you have about your data or how it may be used.

**3.   Third Party Actions  
**

We do not control and are not liable for the actions of any third parties who we may promote and/or link to from this web site. We pride ourselves in recommending quality companies, but have no control over the actions of those third parties, the content they provide, or their privacy practices. While we are not liable for any of the actions of those third parties, you should feel free to give us feedback from time to time on your experiences with any third parties to whom we work with so that we may enhance our future service to all customers.

**4.   Children’s Privacy**

We do not knowingly intend to collect personally identifiable information from children under 18 years of age. If your minor child has provided us with personally identifiable information, you may contact us at the phone number or mailing address listed in the section entitled “Contacting Us” if you want this information deleted from our records. We will then make reasonable efforts to remove your child’s information from the database that stores the information.

**5.   IP Addresses**

We may use your IP address to help prevent fraud, to help diagnose problems with our server, to gather broad demographic information, and to offer you products and services.

**6.   Commitment To Data Security**

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the web site, your information is protected both online and offline.

All information collected from you is stored in a technically and physically secure environment. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, employees, contractors, and vendors who have access to your personally identifiable information in connection with providing services for us are required to keep the information confidential.

We use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, and we do everything we can to protect user information offline. Unfortunately, no transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we take reasonable measures to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of the information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

**7.   Contacting Us**

If you need to contact us, you can email us at success@learntobeabookkeeper.com, call us at 1-307-222-4370, or send us a letter at: 1712 Pioneer Ave., Ste. 622, Cheyenne, WY 82001.

We strive to provide excellent products, along with equally excellent customer service. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our practices, please feel free to contact us using one of the methods listed above.

**8.   Severability**

If any part of this Privacy Policy is held invalid or unenforceable, that portion shall be construed in a manner consistent with applicable law to reflect, as nearly as possible, the original intentions of the parties, and the remaining portions shall remain in full force and effect. 

**9.   Note To California Residents**

If you live in the State of California, under the California Civil Code, you have the right to request that companies who conduct business in California provide you with a list of all third parties to which the company has disclosed Personal Information during the preceding year for direct marketing purposes. 

Alternatively, the law provides that if a company has a Privacy Policy that gives either an opt-out (often referred to as “unsubscribe”) or opt-in choice for use of your Personal Information by third parties (such as advertisers or affiliated companies) for marketing purposes, that the company may instead provide you with information on how to exercise your disclosure choice options. 

This web site qualifies for the alternative option; it has a comprehensive Privacy Policy and provides you with details on how you may either opt-out or opt-in to the use of your Personal Information by third parties for direct marketing purposes. Therefore, we are not required to maintain or disclose a list of the third parties that received your Personal Information for marketing purposes during the preceding year. 

If you are a California resident and want to request information about how to exercise your third party disclosure choices, you must send a request to the following address with a preference on how our response to your request should be sent (email or postal mail). Please send an email to the Privacy Administrator at success@learntobeabookkeeper.com, or you may contact us via regular mail at: 

Bookkeeper Business Launch, LLC  
1712 Pioneer Ave., Ste. 622  
Cheyenne, WY 82001

**All requests sent via regular mail must be labeled “Your California Privacy Rights” on the envelope or post card and clearly stated on the actual request.** For all requests, please include your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. Please include your zip code for our own recordkeeping. 

**We do not accept requests via the telephone or by facsimile.** We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information.
